Women's Studies Program Records UA220
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Workshops and Conferences, 1984 -- 2011; UA220.002; 2.4 Linear Feet; 24 Digital Object(s)
  - [Women of Many Visions] Panel 3, Panel 4 - Casette 4, 1987; UA220.002.005.00011 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Women of Many Visions] Panel 4 - Casette 5, 1987; UA220.002.005.00012 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Forum, 1988; UA220.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - [Faculty Workshop: Integrating Race and Gender into the Curriculum], 1988; UA220.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Race & Gender in the Classroom, 1988; UA220.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - [Race and Gender in the classroom], 1984 -- 1988; UA220.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1989; UA220.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Teaching Series, 1988; UA220.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Teaching Series, 1987 -- 1988; UA220.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Study Group, 1986; UA220.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Teaching race/gender conf, 1987; UA220.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Women's Studies Articles, 1988; UA220.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum - 2nd Faculty Workshop, 1989; UA220.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Classroom Dynamics - Francie Fall, 1989; UA220.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum 88-89, 1988 -- 1989; UA220.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - [Changing our Minds: Transforming the Curriculum, 1989 - photographs], UA220.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - [Changing our Minds: Transforming the Curriculum] Panel 1 Part 1, 1989; UA220.002.005.00027 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Changing our Minds: Transforming the Curriculum] Panel 1 Part 2, 1989; UA220.002.005.00028 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Changing our Minds: Transforming the Curriculum] Panel 2, 1989; UA220.002.005.00029 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Changing our Minds: Transforming the Curriculum] Panel 3, 1989; UA220.002.005.00030 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Curriculum - WPB, 1987 -- 1989; UA220.002.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Tenure & Women, 1997; UA220.002.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Teaching Issues, 1993 -- 1997; UA220.002.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1990; UA220.002.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1991; UA220.002.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1992; UA220.002.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Tufts 1992 Conference, Tape 1, UA220.002.005.00037 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Tufts 1992 Conference, Tape 1, copy, UA220.002.005.00038 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Tufts 1992 Conference, Tape 2, UA220.002.005.00039 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Tufts 1992 Conference, Tape 2, copy, UA220.002.005.00040 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Forum, 1993; UA220.002.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - [Beyond the Classroom 1993 - photographs], UA220.002.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - Forum Award from AAU, 1993; UA220.002.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - [AAUW Legal Advocay Fund Special Distinction Award], 1993; UA220.002.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - WS Colloquium, 1993 -- 1994; UA220.002.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1994; UA220.002.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - [Women at Tufts: The First 100 Years], 1994; UA220.002.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - [1994 Massachusetts AAUW Winter Conference], UA220.002.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - Forum 95 general, 1995; UA220.002.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - Forum 95 - 10th anniversary, 1995; UA220.002.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - Forum: Past Moderators, 1996; UA220.002.005.00051 (Box 5)
  - WS Colloq, 1995 -- 1996; UA220.002.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - WS Senior Awards, 1994 -- 1997; UA220.002.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1997; UA220.002.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - Forum 98 - Samples, 1998; UA220.002.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - Forum: Past flyers, 1987 -- 1997; UA220.002.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - Forum 98: Files, 1998; UA220.002.005.00057 (Box 5)
  - Forum Forms, 1998; UA220.002.005.00058 (Box 5)
  - Planning Forum, 1998; UA220.002.005.00059 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1998; UA220.002.005.00060 (Box 5)
  - Women's Forum, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.002.005.00061
  - WS Senior Awards, 1998; UA220.002.005.00062 (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Classroom 1999 Student Submissions, UA220.002.005.00063 (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Classroom Forum, 1999; UA220.002.005.00064 (Box 5)
  - Doing Feminist Research Workshop, 1999; UA220.002.005.00065 (Box 5)
  - Workshop 99 (Joy Kwesiga), 1999; UA220.002.005.00066 (Box 5)
  - Chinese Women's Conference, 1999; UA220.002.005.00067 (Box 5)
  - Chinese Conference, 1999; UA220.002.005.00068
  - Chinese Studies Women's Studies, 1999; UA220.002.005.00069
  - Chinese Studies Women's Studies, 1999; UA220.002.005.00070
  - Beyond the Classroom Presentations - March, 2000; UA220.002.005.00071 (Box 5)
  - Sr Event - May, 2000; UA220.002.005.00072 (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Classroom, 2000 -- 2004; UA220.002.005.00073 (Box 5)
  - Kounaves Forum Photos, 2002-04-05; UA220.002.005.00074
  - Beyond the Classroom, Mona Damluji submission, 2003; UA220.002.005.00075 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Beyond the Classroom, April, 2004; UA220.002.005.00076 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Guest Speakers 200-2001 Malin Bhattacharya, Charlene Gilbert, Nawal el Saadawi, 2000 -- 2001; UA220.002.005.00077 (Box 5)
  - Coco Fusco, 2000; UA220.002.005.00078 (Box 5)
  - Guest Speakers 2001-2002, Esther Chow 11/2/01, Amy Tsanga 2/15/02, UA220.002.005.00079 (Box 5)
  - Esther Chow jpg, 2001-11-02; UA220.002.005.00080
  - Carmelita Tropicana, 2002; UA220.002.005.00081 (Box 5)
  - Howard Solomon Event 4/9/02, 2002; UA220.002.005.00082 (Box 5)
  - Film Series 02-03, Women Document War & Peace, 2002 -- 2003; UA220.002.005.00083 (Box 5)
  - WS Program 02/03, 2002 -- 2003; UA220.002.005.00084 (Box 5)
  - Sonia and Choomki, 2002-10-19; UA220.002.005.00085
  - Beyond the Classroom - 2005 20th yr, UA220.002.005.00086 (Box 5)
  - 20th Anniversary Seminar, 2005-04-01; UA220.002.005.00087
  - Beyond the Classroom 2005, 2005-04-01; UA220.002.005.00088
  - Sr Event, 2001 -- 2005; UA220.002.005.00089 (Box 5)
  - International Women's Day, 2005; UA220.002.005.00090 (Box 5)
  - International Women's Day 2005, UA220.002.005.00091
  - Kazibwe flyer, 2005; UA220.002.005.00092
  - Kazibwe Presentation, 2005; UA220.002.005.00093
  - Beyond the Forum, 2006; UA220.002.005.00094 (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Classroom 2006, UA220.002.005.00095
  - International Women's Day, 2006; UA220.002.005.00096 (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Classroom, 2007; UA220.002.005.00097 (Box 5)
  - Beyond the Classroom 2007, UA220.002.005.00098
  - International Women's Day, 2007; UA220.002.005.00099
  - Research Colloquium September 2007, UA220.002.005.00100
  - Beyond the Classroom, 2008; UA220.002.005.00101 (Box 5)
  - International Women's Day, 2008; UA220.002.005.00102 (Box 5)
  - International Women's Day proofs 1, 2008; UA220.002.005.00103
  - International Women's Day proofs 2, 2008; UA220.002.005.00104
  - International Women's Day, 2008; UA220.002.005.00105
  - Research Colloquium, 2008-12-01; UA220.002.005.00106
  - International Women's Day, 2009; UA220.002.005.00107
  - International Women's Day, UA220.002.005.00108 (Box 5)
  - Research Colloquium, 2009-11-01; UA220.002.005.00109
  - Sr Event, 2006 -- 2010; UA220.002.005.00110 (Box 5)
  - Senior Presentations, 2006; UA220.002.005.00111
  - Senior Presentations, 2009; UA220.002.005.00112
  - Women's Studies Senior Project Presentations, 2004 -- 2009; UA220.002.005.00113 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Beyond the Forum Flyers], 1986 -- 2011; UA220.002.005.00114 (Box 5)
  - WS Brown Bag Colloquium Series, UA220.002.005.00115 (Box 5)
  - Speaker Ideas, 1997; UA220.002.005.00116 (Box 5)
  - [Event flyers], 1989 -- 1994; UA220.002.005.00117 (Box 5)
  - Conferences - past, 1985 -- 1993; UA220.002.005.00118 (Box 5)
  - Conference flyers, 1996; UA220.002.005.00119 (Box 5)
  - WS Events, 2005 -- 2009; UA220.002.005.00120 (Box 5)